

Seoul, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-5577-5814 | ■ newinh90@gmail.com | # newinh.me | 回 newinh | 🖹 newinh | 🗖 newinh

Summary _

1+ year experience in back-end development. Experienced embedded, Android, iOS development as a beginner, recently worked on project related to collecting data in fashion AI company.

Open culture of IT industry was so impressive that I started developmenting software. As I got help and inspred, I want to be a enginner who can help. Main skills are Python, flask, MySQL now, but i'm ready to challenge other technical skills and accomplish projects.

Skills.

Programming Python, Swift, Java **Frameworks** Flask, Scrapy, pandas Infrastructures AWS, Docker, MySQL

Languages Korea(native), English(Business)

Work Experience _____

Omnious. Co., Ltd. Seoul, S.Korea

BACK-END ENGINEER Nov. 2017 -

Labeling Tool

- · Maintained back-end of in-house web application having 50+ active users for collecting fashion data to train AI model.
 - AWS, Docker, CIrcleCI, Jenkins, Rancher
- Designed RESTful HTTP API, developed server serving them.
 - Python, flask, Swagger, NGINX, uWSGI
- Established relation of domain model, designed database schema.
 - DDD, MySQL
- Built HTTP access logging system and pipeline to store it.
 - fluntd, fluent-bit
- Introduced unit testing, style guide of codebase.

Data Delivery

- Exported collected data based on a rule of extraction to train AI model and processed in a form that is easy to train.
- Established the rule of extraction for data having combinated label, developed a program that parses documented the rule.
- · Automated process from data extraction to data processing, developed CLI to access automated data transfer system.
- · pandas, Celery

Crawler

- Implemented 20+ web crawler for collecting fashion image, developed a scheduling tool for management.
- Built serverless pipeline that stores crawled data in a repository.
- · Scrapy, ScrapingHub, AWS, Zappa

LayGen Inc. Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN

Aug. 2017 - Sep. 2017

Apr. 2017 - May. 2017

- Participated to mnufactoring operating module for a prototype of 3D printer and developed software control the module.
- Developed GUI so that hardware engineer can test controling each part of 3D printer.
- Python, PyQT, Rasberry Pi, Arduino

LINE Corp.

Gyeonggi-do, S.Korea, S.Korea

- Prototyped iOS application "Targted Video" emphasizing object user want in video.
- Used technique of contour extraction, image segmentation and stabilization.
- Implemented video editing function that cuts or pastes object user seleted.
- · Swift, OpenCV

UXEnterprise Seoul, S.Korea

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN Aug. 2016 - Sep. 2016

- Prototyped Android application viewing Femail biorhythm.
- Implemented connection with a measuring device using Bluetooth.
- Java, Android

Education

BoostCamp, Connect Foundation education program

Seoul, S.Korea

Jan. 2017 - Feb. 2017 iOS Course

- Developed iOS Application, "Color to Sound, Sound to Color! ChromaTone"
 - https://github.com/newinh/ChromaTone

Konkuk University

Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN ELECTRONICS

Mar. 2009 - Feb. 2016

• Graduation piece, "IOT Door Lock using Wireless Home Router & Android Device"